hi welcome back to the wheel of life
retreat online retreat kind of cool
right and I'm very pleased to have Joe
shopping Allison helping me to translate
thank you for coming
Holly canal and abundant came across a
covenant so Xiaoping Allison when Jen
DePalma and again thank you and Allison
for thank you incidentally for helping
me for so many years
yeah and you got to come and spend a
moment to fire slobber counter so we're
on this is gonna be online session
number two segments to allow online and
do a stock Monica doo-wop and today
we're gonna do a meditation together
coconut Osama there's a special way to
prepare for a meditation Haku sauce on
the mobile subcommittee Tasi in Tibetan
is called Yin logged in the lumbers of
Tibet dissolute Nocturne pas and these
are seven different steps to prepare
properly for a meditation comfortably
down to cut Medicaid Ellen Bunner and I
know a lot of you have heard them before
SIA power binary understanding darkness
alumina and of course I've been teaching
them for ten years during this normal
teaching
Canas Lamas blue powder alum Remini but
my hope is that and by the way I'd like
to thank a CIA executive director Tim
Luna toppy harapan Jaya done a mimosa
onion between Mecosta component director
executed a CI team la one hop and a very
great father he's really organized this
online which fee online
Amy among all the other things he turn
someone young new calico car and I was
kind of excited to do the retreat
because I think many more people will be
able to enjoy that they don't have to
travel somewhere and spend a lot of
money Salmonella quadra-trac Amica no
Sarah salad even decorum visa doctor
swapped America the propaganda
so I feel like a lot of people who
haven't been able to come to the lower
memory treats in the last 10 years will
be able to attend this one is our
opinion by the pouring on blue basalt
incorrect little ambience llama spot on
track a rainy I can be some Hardy Aryan
subtly me and so I think it's good for
all of us if we can just review these
preliminaries to meditation - these are
peaking on the back on top maninjau
humbly from the whole uncontaminated see
me
and so I apologize if you heard these
seven steps before did you say momentum
off Chicka under Saddam enough to Jalan
kayu sebelum Nia but I think they're
extremely important and I myself do them
almost every day top is a bigger more
like a song upon tendons I'm like ooh
can you guess the party I like to say
that you know you can't run a race in
the Olympics
if you don't warm up first sorry the
olympia Domino South Alameda holder and
I think it's easier to warm up your body
then it is through warming up your mind
dance is ought to be moved on to Mona's
canto under epidemic on what can't be
Karen when I was young and I was first
learning to drive a car because I am a
semen and blood under a movie which
Alison promised to learn this year
listen Jen gentlemen plodding about Nene
I remember the teacher told us first
thing the teacher told us sorry incoming
guru kanakam when you get in your car
walked on the muscle come on Bo
start the car y'all economists in and
then wait for three or four or five
minutes
Cambodian Tonga think empathically mama
need don't drive it right away
javelin someone darania because car
needs time to warm up mama be able to
walk tanto como no son and he said your
car will last twice as long if you were
me nibble on mobile and uh convert and
or call in a bloomin chicken taco
contamination and you know who the last
used car I had when I lived here
because truculence I am a lucky cat
because I attend all this uni it was
almost 30 years old and more they have
beer think a proton
and it lasted fine for 30 years
Jensen never could've joined him in
bikes la mattina blue Tahoe in fact it's
still really I gave it to my friend back
on mobile AMA cinch island and Simon
Bricker company taman sari that's a big
piece of knowledge for everyone
warm up your car daddy told us about
pocket oven but sharmaji see a pop open
a skull mobile anger just for five
minutes
honey Aslam money money there's a
there's a heat hot and cold needle in
your car it goes like this understanding
any mobile I so wait until the needle
goes off a coat you need to know
something Jeremy I'm an incompetent
opinion
and meditation is the same MIDI toss
into kasama so I've been meditating for
I don't know over 40 years
so da Rimini tosses lomilomi done impact
low down and I still cannot start a
meditation called dance I am a CNBLUE
bisa Mamula metatarsal Olive Garden
Damian
even after 40 over 40 years of
meditating I need to warm up my
meditation line before I start
meditating Bobby Darin pollutant Berman
it is I am a super luminous can pick a
little on fire male and that warm-up has
become a very enjoyable and precious
part of my life
done Tamino sunny totally menjadi sought
a second opinion on Condon banking
Veronica Della bitta fire
so I actually in the morning and I look
forward to having coffee and meditation
more money house I do go walk to minim
copy done maybe touch the papa rasta so
we're gonna do that warm up together
la coka ominous on bersama and then I'm
gonna teach you to other kinds of
meditation sort of more months Osaka
manager can do a janice mediator Celina
Saperstein so much of a Manasa and in my
opinion Don menorah 2 ponyo ponyo all of
your meditations some women leaders
younger you could every day you could
choose one of these three warm-ups to
put in your military so tell peri under
be some Emilio Salazar to the radhika
antennas Vimanas ensemble america see
the first warmer / - + / tama
which is called the seven part warmer
noticeable to debug and ominous on its
focus is one of the teachers in your
life for castillo de las olas otaku rue
de la Vida Panda
and the theory behind that warmer than
theory develop ominous a neato
it's called suction suction it's about
Sokcho
so suck means just before you do your
main meditation sub-grantee supplement a
block you can meditate Sudama try to
collect some real quick good common
among a bull condom wrapper karma asleep
icon at the top and john means the
jumper Aarthi just before you start your
main meditation some bloom under mom'll
immediate assault on try to clean some
bad seeds out of your mind trouble on
top number second Bob Republic poor Gary
picking on anger and I don't know right
now it's a spring in Arizona when I'm
talking
Melanie Adela Muslims the media is on
and it of a favorable Chara
this is the actual week that we are
planting most of our garden in your
dilemma Gustav github anonymous o began
Broussard Erica Bandito first we do the
job from atomic atomic Oh conjunct we
get rid of other old dirty leaves and
old problems in the soil we clean the
soil it doesn't care can someone down to
one masala dhaba see Canton Anya when
you're preparing for a meditation
soft wonder membership committee tau C
it's very very sweet to clean any bad
seeds you made in the last 24 hours
I can someone is on top of a second baby
baroque young under pendulum diplomas on
track here so don't try to think of all
the bad things you did in your life you
will never start your meditation
elements Obamacare can someone be bit
broken under Penelope no Karnataka no
mama llama detox see it's very powerful
and it's enough to just think about the
main
Bad Seeds you might have planted in the
last 24 hours
any son got co-opted and took up on
eleven but be careful Tom Donilon
Pancham track here
then you did a sock fight sock means
make some instant good karma Lake
Okanagan sock Umbra are teaming what
karma
tannenberg goose
so John is like cleaning out the soil
making it clean for the new plant the
region under lasa bottom embrace I can't
animal body abrasion Tottenham on Nauru
and in Sark is kinda like put fertilizer
in some water and then caboodle sucks
optimum Britpop octants ticket I of the
tournament and the plan is your
meditation dantana Manya dalamud it
agenda now the easiest way to clean away
your bath is the easiest way to plant
some new goods probably people to invite
one of the teachers in your life with
you guru de Medici Brasa manga so these
seven steps for preparing for meditation
32 Juhu lung capacity up on top minute
assini they're all based on one of your
teachers someone who deserves our
company solo song guru under later in
this series of 25 videos 90 de Cerio
uploaded my video innie I'll teach you a
special way to prepare for your
meditation so you can monitor it under
Turkish Ottoman perception medica see
which is more based on shemitah yella
b-but reassortant schemata and geometry
means making your mind very very
peaceful so you can see emptiness then
Shama table our team about picking under
Sun hats on optimizing under some hot
cocoa Solomon so sometimes we'll do the
seven steps formula koukin - too long
tiny focused on earth one of our
teachers for focus for the salah satu
guru gita but sometimes the preparation
for meditation this month the peter card
impressive amount of Miletus Ebola Nene
we'll be a traditional preparation for
shaman amenities akan menjadi press upon
traditional of meditation schemata which
is making the mind cry enough to see
emptiness yeah I told me about picking
on took money hot cocoa someone and then
we'll have a third kind of meditation
warm-up coming up on our sanity and that
will be based on emptiness it's tough so
many to sendiri so three kinds of warmer
the other to gamma Champa Manasa and
today we're gonna do this seven step
warm up together
koukin Pomona Sun conjunct hombre
sama-sama and it's based on our teacher
don't anybody else walk on guru kita
we'll be choosing one of the teachers in
our life chameleon salah satu guru dalam
he Tokita of course the most powerful
example would be your heart teacher if
you have a hard teacher on top on in
Candela guru happy under cheek and
openness or on guru happy the short
definition of a hard teacher definitely
think about a guru happy it's the
teacher who helped you the most in this
life under law sovereign guru the second
one but one God Allah P to penny
so you can use that would be the most
common example of teacher to use for
this manatee the undergrad mangu now can
you talk about the topic and guru
totally tossing but you could use other
teachers in your life can be someone
good not and para guru Angad a Levite
Amanda your dad and your mom where we
first great teachers I under need board
Allah guru pitamah Anja and then
obviously in your school life you met
everyone met a few special teachers in
their life
adelante dupont scholar and a step or
alberto modem and guru special de la
vida marika sometimes is not a school
teacher sometimes it's a sport teacher
or an art teacher or a music teacher
talk about any book on gurus call a
panagon don't grow arigato guru Sonia
the Guru Massey
later on you met someone who taught you
how to do your occupation your job
comedian and abrupt amudha menses or
anemia Chaka Khan pocono John Buchan
Ganga that's a special teacher in our
line Gurukul so slalom in Akita if
you're married then your wife or husband
is it is a great teacher in your life
you can do so Dominica maka Istria Tommy
and and the language capital on people
if you have children those are great
teachers you can opinion Ricard Allah
good in him even in your middle age you
your parents we were elderly are nice
teachers to have in you know but can you
see apparel belongs to under Lancia the
Ligurian bike de la vida Unger you can
if you don't have a hard teacher you can
tuck it up by mimicking guru hearty you
can also just imagine one undertook a be
some of my own candy and you could bring
that teacher to prepare for these seven
steps of meditation then under be some
of our guru tanto members have come to
Jalan committee Cassini
and of course you could take your
historical teachers to Santander be
someone gunned down guru his stories
could be Buddha Buddha Jesus Muhammad
Muhammad Moses Moosa Confucius also
cloud-to-cloud many many choices might
not be now just in the last few weeks
the lumber Papa bingo tractor my
personal favorite has been negligent are
you going to me for for it prima di and
Allah Arya Nagarjuna so I've been doing
the 7 steps with him yes I am lakukan to
do long condom Monday and then every I
don't know every three weeks or so you
can change the teacher or every day if
he would lie lose captain coming what
Allah P under missile Megantic guru I
tossed a body to kendama so the picture
we used to introduce this segment come
out come suck Malini it shows a monk
walking down a country road and a lot
number sort of mixture Sundberg element
new Sri Jolanda so and I've I've visited
many times the place where the gardener
is supposed to have been born in and
studied done sire so just a moment you
meet and pacquiao under a lot upon layer
on top applaud your Nagarjuna
into that miscalled better you the
lumber sultan but it'll support better
you kinda like the land of the coconuts
support a janasthana kalapa so I always
imagined when I when I think of me guys
man so slalom abuyin can catacomb a
mechanic's garage una I don't like to
close my eyes and think about a painting
come on Tommy Kirk on location were spot
on
I like to think of the gardener walking
down a road to his house I also come
Americana gonna do Newbridge elementary
challenger almost like a real prison leo
support your own son gohan it's somehow
I imagine he's very kind of funny person
and tombow mono saya suka mom I can do
some agura your son at Lu su and
extremely than selection sort of does
and extremely moral done some of our
moral and a great understanding
emptiness is why he sometimes he's
called the Arya harmony Austin Danko
song and Ana Patrick and Emily on
disability area so let's start our seven
steps
Marika Tom moonlight into Lanka if you
don't know how to prepare your
meditation space you can deduct out our
mobile hot chef can wrong meditation or
the correct path to a poster tube
webinar I taught it in the first two
years of the ten years so I am gonna do
a tone parameter is pollutant in me and
I suggest you go check it on the
knowledge base and a mentor in the
knowledge base and I'll ask him to put
the link up for you so I can mamita
payment of manaro Tonto Conda
at the end of this video they are
carefully doing me okay so let's get
ready to meditate okay Mario more
Minotaur see the main thing is to be
comfortable
now what Amidala Morrisania man there
was comfortable place in my house is my
couch messiah allah sofa and i meditate
on this and it's just very comfortable
to me so sit somewhere where you don't
have to move the need to do cloudy tompa
under dr. Luber graph and set up
standard across
it's always good to put some questions
to raise the back of your pickle bottom
rubber band on top man I can imagine
block an angle under your hands are
comfortable on your legs and I get a spa
ha
anyway that's comfortable for you Papa
and Mama not to come down sometimes I
will put a small cushion in my lap chill
debunk one and I'd like to rest my hands
they're done so come another time I'm
sorry idea toss yeah
most important is your back is straight
up punting on dialog on the loose
small smile on your face city cats on
your money be beer
don't you know crunch up your face don't
wrinkle don't frown gentleman can watch
judge and encrypt and Johnson Road
okay here we go mari kita boleh
the mouth should not be too tired
monitamon terlalu Tagum the lips should
be relaxed
maybe rah-rah so relax the forehead gdv
legs now he harus relaxed the eyelid
should be nice cluck Matos auto said to
go sometime
the hand should be relaxed Bunga relax
the back is straight on Google's the
shoulder blades are pressed together and
your chest comes out a little bit blah
blah who did a and and addict work
on certificate which means that your
hands might come back often work on your
thighs then on your knees haha and Jerry
look it's very good for your posture
posture and if your lower abdomen jacket
monkian Bawa is firm to get the
contraction but not you know pulled in
with effort and so saw fire so how did
get that firm abdomen which gives you a
strong back Saruman bought broken tongue
young but open Canyon quote there is a
there's a nice trick I got taken Bacchus
when you breathe out kanga compose the
boss and you finish your out-breath and
katika sloth I then consciously try to
push out a little more air from your
lungs indicate levy by the Kudarat oh
and that was tiny chunk and brought
Megan Dhamma and that will make it
easier to sit up straight
any talk and what kita sala beem would
go to cook up so let's start with ten
breaths
mari kita monotonous
a person before we start the first of
the seven steps Sablan get a mullah
Lanka Pomodori to JoVE lanka very slow
exhale cally at the end of the exhale
press a little more breath oh yeah do
killaby by Nicole okay don't worry about
the in-breath it will take care of
itself
German quarter-ton tongue here open a
postcard a token tragedies nearly make
sure lower abdomen is tightening
slightly as you at the end of the
outbreak was taken to the dungeon Mohan
don't you can tongue constantly kept you
can have goose on AAPIs pushing out the
last bit of air from your Knights naked
man Kentucky are very pooper Wanda it
will also prevent a buildup of prana or
a new Lord Chief you need to happen when
took up a new partner I don't know about
she and then you won't feel you won't
get feeling some nervousness as you
meditate
cottonmouths are goo cop swap toma la
coka meditation smile smile Sarika
personal i later sir cluck Mata hollows
nice T 10 long exhales market Alacoque
ins Paulo hombu sana pass Pancham
you
now we'll start the first of the seven
warm up steps
scarran katakana you'll imagine pertama
there in two children couple minor son
invite one of those teachers to come to
sit with you guru it onto the person
could be any of those stitches we talked
about mrs. Hollis Otto Goren so they get
a bit arakan very powerful person to
such child with them or
melaka construction in america very
powerful for planting good see it's very
powerful for cleaning bad seeds some
autonomy big bug goes down so that
Quattro CC can be bit more oh and you
invite them and they come and sit in
front of you and I wouldn't done but I
cut American determined adopted upon
under on the same level they think
attend summer I like to say knee to me
Kabuto do you understand they are not a
statue or a painting done team of
America become part on auto location
it's a real person in front of me
recorder so who ended up on fire I can
see their chest moving with your breath
so every summer accepted onion burger
cleanin up as America I can feel the
subtle warmth from their body knee to
knee so every summer osakan cotton
hollow spirit of America very noted
Cooper good people have a certain
delicate fragrance to do foreign bank
mobility aroma a lambo Toronto like a
very subtle Jasmine's me supporting bow
horrible atoms on a nose so
teachers image in front of you it's not
a painting it's a real prison
the detour car number guru an agreed
upon and book on Lucas Santa Parramatta
your eyes are closed Martin guitar to
toe but their eyes are opened up Emmitt
America Trabuco they are looking at us
humidity but I come here under SWAT law
and government in very very pleased with
you the military brats and a million
under a sudden drama detoxing they just
enjoy being with them so company party
work to blossom America we're gonna
meditate together data confirm editor
super summer
you
the second of the seven worm up steps
Lanka can wander into to Lanka Pomona
Sun is to make a lot of friend to your
teacher and a llama but person behind
copper a good Wanda and it just sets the
feeling of the meditation is very happy
Danny - honey I monitor Prasanna hot
mahadji Aslam a minute RC so imagine any
beautiful gift today by Raja Bahadur
young India could be I think in the
garden and light coconut Cyrus and
Arjuna suka klaapa there's a traditional
offering to to imagine the whole sky
covered with flowers and traditional
vehicles little long until 2:00 p.m. and
boom and make this suffering person
bimini there's a very special offering
or somebody else a lot special to your
teacher what oh grow under and that is
to God down to the teacher
in total about should cover the Guru ito
by thinking about some beautiful quality
that I heard the member bcurtin topical
it was Indian by Camilla key so I'm
thinking of Arya Nagar a traditional
mummy kirkin Arya Nagar tuna good humor
funny person who Morris young bike
Coronel ooh - extremely brilliant
somewhat brilliant and knows how to
write beautiful beautiful short things
than powder Amidala Saahil pentakill
India so I just appreciate the gardener
you desire a container mahogany Arjuna
and that's a higher offering Dhoni total
a person body and pollen thingy you
appreciate your own teacher and my gurus
endearing
you
the third of the seven preparation steps
Lanka category to do Lanka Prosser upon
is to clean away the third seat you've
made in the last 24 hours under a llama
but secondly big broken under tandem de
l'homme de plumage on track here so
spend a few minutes to open your heart
tell you know come open up a minute
momoka hockey under let your teacher
look inside we work on guru Malayalam
and show them the mistakes you have made
in the last 24 hours
don't talk about America course all
under proper column do punch on track
here don't be shy travel maloo maloo be
completely honest but a judge or loss of
Pannonia and that kind of willingness to
show you teacher your mistakes Granicus
ambiance amata mikono Solomon talked
about a guru and to promise them you'll
try harder today member johnty covered
America under Congress Ajala be cross
Harini this kills the soul that sees a
meme Abu Dhabi big big big Brooke too
and that will make your meditation much
sweeter
got me talking about me Natasha under
job Lobby Mandy's firstly I like to
spend 10 breaths on each of the seven
steps
star Opry bodies are so common Gouda can
spoon up as Podesta planetary Tatanka
sometimes xx my mind is is kind of busy
Percodan go Appa Lucci kappa
krautscience Pertino Sybil
you
in our preparation step number four
Scott I'll brush up on Lanka compa we're
gonna balance thinking about the Bad
Seeds you talkin in bunkin put me kill
intent on baby burrow
alright thinking about some good seeds
within drop a hole back and get a la la
coca it's very much human nature sunup
Medusa window for to focus on our
mistakes
what the Espada castle on kita and
we don't give equal time to the good
things within don't get ot dogma breakin
walked in some on to how how a bike and
get up I'll holla koukin so now 10
relaxed breath Jerry's Quran lakukan
Spallone a pissant I thinking about the
sweetest things you did mostly for other
people in the last 24 hours
Pinkerton Tahoe drama mr. Mandela koukin
cannot occur on the laptop low bunch on
track here you can you can include your
meditation time
somebody so swatting under so Kai okay
here we go ten bells
okay Monica Thailand Judkins pull on
AAPIs what are some of the sweet things
you did in the last 24 hours
Apollo Manisha and Ella koukin Delano
plumage on track here for other people
on top or online
you
and now we're ready for the fifth of the
seven preparation steps Quran Kitab on
to Plunkett Lima Gary - Jalan commercial
pun and in our mind we ask our teacher
to continue teaching us
dunh dunh a picture and keep a memento
good on the cross manager remember that
the teachers teaching can come to us in
many ways
inaudible Anubis undertook Okita la
banda Katara
oh sure sometimes we get a video talking
about the steps to the time goddamn
katomina butkin video Tantallon Khadija
lon maybe we read a scripture MOOC in
Cataumet solution suci maybe we go to
listen to a teacher in person
monkey Nikita insurance Odin guru sir
Alonso but negative things also teaches
a lot toppy how far we got gift you
could be some orange or Akita the
challenges and disappointments in our
life they often teach us more than the
successes untangled I'm Koka Chauhan
dalam hijab breaker sorry manager katana
be de repente a cobra how Sealand
so here in this fifth step to being
Lanka clean money it can be a kind of
surrender support the Centennial menorah
teacher or guru please teach me
voluntary saya let good teachings come
to me we are adjourned bike-a-thon
kepada saya and let difficult teachings
come to me the Jerusalem to God that on
casaya and I will have courage than fire
company macabre Mian our Bistro fire
commander equal and I will also learn
from the difficult parts in my life
don't side to on blood-shod area
monkey became sullied Alameda
so I trust you to this Airport i under
send me sweet thermal teachings karim
khan fire under under my arm a nice but
please also send me difficult teachings
problems in my life
papito long to kill him
jerilyn sulit masala and Amitabh saya
like very challenging viruses superb if
es rossi on solid momentum and I will do
my best to become a better person from
these challenges and Sock'em lakukan and
her bike on top menjadi orang led by
continental aleni
then when difficult situations come to
you please remember you asked your
teacher to send a look at the gasket
oscillator Judy Hara ping up a
biomimetic or ammonium Canyon and don't
get discouraged and don't get off
balance
Don John Burkett's al hockey Jonathan
Kozol in bong-gun used them to become
stronger good knuckle America up Mandela
be cool when difficult times come to you
use it as a reason to serve more people
Smok Tomas also later Judy good now
consumer guy Allison talk Malayan
alleppey by Nikora this virus is an
excellent time for Buddhist virus any
other Lamas can tap at Monkeyman
Buddhist this is a great opportunity to
show other people what is a Buddhist in
the pattern banco santander ducal
Commodore online up by Tucson Buddhist
the more dangerous life is samake and he
to proper higher the more financial
trouble we had smokey and by that masala
finish Allan Kittleman Ikki there were
doubts and fears the people here so
makimba nicaraguan kakouton young neha
dhupia a real buddhist person so steps
up this is their time to to show how
much they can help people so long
buddhist and jocund module in your
element American took money to convert
up American depend on man - Orin if a
Buddhist person has a face mask that
another person does not have a face mask
because our own Buddhist Maliki
Muscovado nor am i get a moment keenya
the buddhist person happily gives the
face mastered
what I'm Buddhist and insanity memory
mascara whatta you tawkin online and
we're happy we had the chance to do it
don't get us an animal akiko-san
pattanayaka conure
you
sixth preparation step monk approach
oppan kangnam
is to ask this teacher to stay in her
life and allow moment our guru in eating
of the libido kita as tempted not to
live our life momentum ricotta de
Kooning Coconino pita the Karma the good
sister have a teacher karma a table be
beaten by canto America guru they are
perhaps the most rare seeds in the world
but a common can be bitten Pauline Lanka
dunya and may I always plant our seeds
to have you in my life than smoke Esaias
l-'alamin an ability taunt of mammalian
development of saya sustained minor
pollen Tata progeny hit up saya
you
seventh step in the meditation long
cockatoo to de la maleta see the last
one here it comes after the actual
meditation tragedy still amadito sits on
the burner so you do these six steps
that we just did jeonggi under la
Cucaracha kita lakukan then you do your
actual meditation which might be one of
the steps of the path lalume la coka
meditation Sumner young monk Ananda
Lassa Lassa to Lanka Gary Jalan like a
death meditation support a minute as a
comedian or an emptyness meditation at
America psychic or solvent or a Tumlin
exchanging sorry giving and taking
meditation a tomlin meditation one braid
and mugambi exchanging myself and others
at umberto calvini in an online and then
after you finish the meditation does
lost lost five minute I see you think
about all of the good seeds you planted
by doing the meditation and over Michiel
can someone be bit by can understand I'm
gonna cook on MIDI kasi and then you
very consciously put them in the bank
man come on under the Gunn Sunderman
Arun and debunk when you dedicate any
good seed to another person's happiness
stop and Amla koukin did occur see me be
done by canto companion or online then
that seed is protected and it will
always stay with you Liberty totally
Linda Madonna comes la la brasa manga so
paradoxically Judy para talks yeah you
keep the seat by giving it away and I
limp on the bitumen lubricant you so the
seventh step of meditation the Dylan
cockatoo - ready Darcy after your main
meditation is completed so Allah made it
a few Tom on the slow side then imagine
that you are sharing the good seeds you
planted by meditating wallow by aankhen
vivid Pakistan and upon under the burma
titisee and you are sending them out to
all the people in this world
kanya customer on you do me a nice start
with people who are in the same room
well I landed on me wrong I'm sama then
share those good seeds with other people
in your neighborhood
chameleon buggy can be bit bike into the
van or online d-link woman under
instantly sees there are the people in
your city
lalu kidding me bitter cusamano Nakata
under and share them with everyone in
your country and buggy comes someone yet
again some more on the maganda then
share them with everyone in this planet
somebody on my buggy never go somewhere
on the planet beanie and then send them
out to outer space to share with other
people living in other worlds coming at
him toward a suburban didn't answer mo
our onion think of the dunya line
there's a tradition to do this
sharing a Gertrud DC lakukan Pamunkey
enemy of the good seeds of our
meditation be bit by Thierry migitus
Akita by imagining the seeds as a golden
life then one by Anton big big big
potatoes about gets a higher mass and at
the end of our meditation then the Akira
Maeda tsuki tah
we will take at least three very very
slow deep exhales kaka'ako constant
activity column yourself good season
c'mon you can do so to share them with
other people but about getting on or
online as a beautiful goal in life the
llama talk to hire a Muslim in de ok
let's do it together
ok Mariquita lakukan bersama
you
one last suggestion about your
meditation Soto salandrich el puntal
meditation de and then we're finished
with this second segment and this
month's practice in quito slow sliding
and began a meal at the end bula Mimi so
I've been meditating for over 40 years
so does Islam Allah Peter impact luta
but there have been periods in my life
appear the period early on a bit of SIA
when I got I became busy swap dose I am
enjoy the simple maybe I was too busy
teaching meditation MOOC in Seattle
illusive of Mohammed eaten see and I
didn't have time to do my own medicine
I just wanted to tell you that this will
happen to every meditator once are you
handing in my burrito and behind me a
continuity but a stability at all and
then don't get very disturbed the editor
monitor Gangu when you're ready kappa
Candice you start your meditations again
Malala Burma DITA solanki and what I've
learned after many years of meditating
and a banks I applaud your account under
MIDI Tasi
start with very short meditations Milan
London and meditation sonnets in 15
minutes
limo blast minute 20 minutes - Apollonia
start back or begin meditation with
short ones
melanca Bali a Tamil Eelam editor see
young pendant then once a week Lala step
mingu in crystals meditations but just
one minute mainly toss a 208 Amba
they're not subtle money so this week 15
minutes the dimming we nearly my blossom
on it every day
step hurry same time is helpful walk
down some akan
vermin fat then on Sunday lalu Domingo
increased 16 minutes Samba menjadi end
of last minute and the next Sunday
Sunday increased 17 Herriman cobra
cotton t tomba when the DTG blossoming
and in this way they interfere they will
begin to the Lambs tongue a typhoon
you will have a very good 4050 minutes
of meditation and below some aluminum
can within a year you'll have a very
good one hour of meditation can be some
lakukan bonita same box Lama saw to jump
and that's our goal Donita to join kita
to have one hour of meditation today
want to be some la coka milita's Islam
was a to jump so hard you build up to
one hour
tockman top I saw to jump which is
perfect for seeing emptiness some poor
not really hot cocoa song slowly open
your eyes become a table honey take a
good stretch lakukan Brandon Thank You
Ellen for just three Mikasa Alison on
top top Yamaha and see you guys in
segment 3 done some packet amudha
Stockman katika